#### Contact

276-696-1163 (Mobile) jdm7dv@virginia.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/jdm7dv (LinkedIn) www.jonathanmoore.net (Personal)

Top Skills

**WPF** 

C++

Visual Studio

Honors-Awards

Honor Society
Webby Award
Royal Society Of The Arts
Fellowship

# Sir Jonathan Moore

I run an Ableton User Group in the Tri-Cities, Propellerhead Rack Extensions and contribute to the Apache Foundation.

Abingdon, Virginia

# Summary

I began my professional career right out of high school in technical support and development as a Macromedia User Group then later worked for Adobe and FreeBSD volunteer and contributor. At the same time pursuing my associates and bachelors in computer science. I graduated summa cum laude from Tenn. Tech and a UVa alumni. I was also a web developer for the UVa-Wise Magazine. And member of the ACM. My complete discography is available on Bandcamp. I'm a BMI writer and publisher. I have been streamed worldwide with Tunecore And developed some small VST's and Rack Extensions for Propellerhead and Steinberg which never shipped. I recently became a Microsoft Visual Studio industry partner and created a Microsoft Research and Innovation group on Gitlab. Also trying to find some time for sound design and amateur asteroid hunting with MPC. I'm in the Virginia and National Associations for the Gifted since 2011 and Mensa groups here on LinkedIn And IEEE Computer Society also a member of the Mensa High IQ society on LinkedIn I also have been a Microsoft MVP. I am wanting to pursue gifted studies at the University of Connecticut maybe. I scored a 140 on the Mensa mobile app. . Sixtrack is the infrastructure that helps upgrade the LHC.

# Experience

Adobe

Senior Software Engineer September 2018 - Present

I contribute to Apache Flex, Google Closure and FlexJS at the Apache Foundation and the Adobe Exchange Partner Program.

Ableton Organizer October 2017 - Present

User Group Organizer, and Github User Group Engineer.

Page 1 of 3

https://www.ableton.com/en/community/user-groups/tri-cities-ableton-user-group/

https://github.com/AbletonTriCitiesUserGroup

https://abletontricitiesusergroup.com/

https://www.linkedin.com/company/ableton-tri-cities-user-group/

Propellerhead Software Senior Software Development Engineer April 2016 - Present

Rack Extension Developer

Broadcast Music, Inc. (BMI) Electronic Musician March 2005 - Present Abingdon, Va

Deal with MTV, HBO, Showtime NBC and CBS

#### Microsoft

Senior Software Development Engineer October 2005 - February 2019 (13 years 5 months)

Currently at individual status. And a linked Microsoft Research Github. And owner of the Microsoft Research Group on Gitlab. Former Office 365 Partner. My Abelton User Group is A Microsoft Partner.

#### Macromedia

Technical Support

December 2000 - October 2006 (5 years 11 months)

Originally a Macromedia User Group focusing on Flash special FX and UI prototyping. Also Director Shockwave. Then Adobe employee.

Foresight Institute Member 2004 - 2005 (2 years)

AVID Audio Visual Installation & Design Audio Engineer April 2002 - December 2004 (2 years 9 months) Originally Digidesign, Digidesign Partner

## **Grand Home Furnishings**

Porter

February 1996 - November 1998 (2 years 10 months)

Bristol, Va

# Education

## **Udemy Academy**

Complex Systems Theory, Complex Adaptive Systems, Estate Planning and Trusts.  $\cdot$  (2018 - 2021)

#### edX

Computer Music, Artifical Intelligence, Computation Structures · (2015 - 2021)

## Stanford University

Stanford Online, Quantum Mechanics for Scientists and Engineers · (2016)

## University of Virginia

Bachelor of Science, Computer Software Engineering · (2008 - 2013)

Tennessee College of Applied Technology - Nashville

Associate's Degree, Computer Science · (1999 - 2001)